Yeah
This ain’t a game and you know
we don’t play
You ain’t never seen the typa show we
boutta show ya
You ain’t never heard this typa flow
we crashing on ya
Tidal wave, tidal wave, it’s about to go
You will never dominate,
domino when I see you fall
Know I pop better get back
Hand in my pocket
Watch the rocket blow
우리 걱정은 딱히 넣어둬 빨리
Look at me on a roll
Let bygones be bygones
I ain’t never had no problems
That high road we gon’ walk over
Cause icons be icons
Whatchu gon’
Whatchu gon’ do
Lookin’ good
Lookin’ fly
Lookin’ brand new
Unbelievable
어림없거든
어이없거든 (You love it love it)
When we pull up, know it’s all on site
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N we up, up, up
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
Up like whoa can you feel us feel us
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
This is how we do it
We go whoa oh oh oh
Copy copy copy copy, till the error pop up
Copy copy, wanna be me
but you’re never gonna
They all eatin’ my leftovers
I left over what’s left over
Like ring ring, come and get closer
We take over, that’s game over
Nobody do it like this
Nobody nobody do it like this
You’re never catching me slip
I switch it on with a flick of the wrist
Let bygones be bygones
I ain’t never had no problems
That high road we gon’ walk over
Cause icons be icons
Whatchu gon’
Whatchu gon’ do
Lookin’ good
Lookin’ fly
Lookin’ brand new
Unbelievable
어림없거든
어이없거든 (You love it love it)
When we pull up, know it’s all on site
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N we up, up, up
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
Up like whoa can you feel us feel us
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
This is how we do it
We go whoa oh oh oh
우린 보란듯이
Yeah we run it up, run it up
불을 지필 거야
Burn it up, burn it up
세상 꼭대기에
Say my name, say my name
우린 판을 바꿀 Game changer uh uh
Definition dangerous, dangerous
Clock is ticking, ticking
Buckle up, buckle up
Bet you never met a monster like me
I’ll never stop, don’t forget
we gon’ make history
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N
We go up like whoa
우린 Killas killas
우린 Villains villains
Up high for me baby
High for me baby oh
This is how we do it
We go whoa oh oh oh
We go up